(Amy:)Oh, well, you know,
now-now that I'm hearing it,
it does sound familiar.
(Sheldon:)How could it?
(Sheldon:)I never told you,
and you never bothered to ask.
(Amy:)Well, now I know.
Yeah.
(Meemaw:)So, Penny, I understand
you have a new job.
(Penny:)Yes.
(Penny:)I'm a pharmaceutical
sales rep.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Meemaw:)It's so wonderful that
you modern gals can have it all.
(Meemaw:)A husband
and a full-time career.
(Amy:)I have a relationship
and a full-time career, too.
(Meemaw:)That doesn't bode well.
Why not? You-you just said
it's okay for her to work.
(Meemaw:)Well, Leonard doesn't need as
much tending to as Sheldon does.
(Meemaw:)And as Moon Pie explained,
(Meemaw:)Leonard's work
(Meemaw:)is more of a hobby.
(Leonard:)That's my best friend.
(Penny:)Yeah.
AMY:
Look,
I-I get that you're protective
of your grandson,
(Amy:)but he's an adult now.
(Amy:)Maybe I understand what he needs
better than you do.